准备好了吗  孩子们
Are you ready, kids?
好了船长
Aye aye, captain
我听不见
I can't hear you
好了船长
Aye aye, captain
是谁住在深海的大菠萝里
Who lives in a pineapple under the sea?
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
方方黄黄伸缩自如
Absorbent and yellow and porous is he
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
如果四处探险是你的愿望
If nautical nonsense be something you wish
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
那就敲敲甲板让大鱼开路
Then drop on the deck and flop like a fish
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
准备
Ready
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
我们爱圈圈
编剧
分镜总监
翻译: 1440kHz
指导总监
动画总监
统筹
监制
本字幕仅限学习交流
严禁用于商业用途
藻床小朋友
现在回到藻床小朋友
And now back to "The Kelpbed Kids"
藻床小朋友这片子也太好笑了
"The Kelpbed Kids" are hilarious
击掌
High four
不知道为什么是黑白的
Wonder why it's in black and white
这种选择很有艺术气息
It's a "artistical" choice
好了  藻床小朋友
All right, Kelpbed Kids
快给我从实招来
Youse gonna spill the beans
你们把糖果藏到
about where you hide all your candy
这俱乐部什么地方  不然就完了
in this here clubhouse or else
绝不告诉你  阿贾克斯
Not to you, Ajax
我们不可能告诉你就藏在柜子里
We'll never tell you that it's in the cabinet
真对不起
Sorry, gang
派大星  这藻床小朋友是不是
Hey, Patrick, don't the Kelpbed Kids
有点像我们认识的熟人
kinda look like people we know?
熟人个个我都不认识
I don't know any people we know
你说柜子啊
The cabinet, you say
圈圈
Hoops?
糖果
嗨  阿贾克斯
Hi, Ajax
是空的
It's empty
我一定要让大家
I'm gonna give everyone here
还有家里老子  全都吃我一拳
and their old man a knuckle sandwich
好啊
Oh boy
配奶酪吃吗
With cheese?
配奶酪吃
With cheese
休想得逞  呆呆小呆瓜
Oh, no you don't, you dizzy ding dong
搞什么
What gives?
放开我
Let me go
你被圈住了
You just got hooped
圈圈  圈圈
Hoops, Hoops
就这么定了
That settles it
我们最爱的藻床小朋友就是圈圈
Hoops is our favorite Kelpbed Kid
拿出我们的官方正品圈圈呼啦圈吧
Let's get out our official Hoops hoops
我昨天在海贝网上买的
that I bought on SeaBay
早就想到了  兄弟
Way ahead of ya, pally
我的缩小了
Mine shrunk
没事  派大星
Oh, no, Patrick
大小可以调
It's adjustable
圈圈不一定非得是个圈
Who says a hoop has to be round?
啊对
Oh, yeah
有个宽松调整按钮
There's a relaxed-fit button
我呼啦圈上面被谁写满了东西
Someone wrote all over my hula hoop
圈圈
裤头村大街17号
上面印了个地址
There's an address printed on here
就在裤头村里
And it's in Bikini Bottom
你觉得圈圈会不会就住在那
Do you think it's where Hoops lives?
可以吗
Could we?
应该吗
Should we?
按了他家门铃就跑吗
Ring his doorbell and run away?
不对
No
拿厕纸撒满他家
Toilet-paper his house?
不对
No
把他的普通咖啡换成无咖啡因的
Switch out his regular for decaf?
不对
No
是可以去见他
We can meet him
明白
Gotcha
可以去见他  然后拿厕纸撒满他家
We can meet him, then toilet-paper his house
他喝完咖啡一定用得上
He's gonna need it after the coffee
我们到了
This is it--
圈圈家
where Hoops lives
好一个豪宅
It's a palace
我太紧张  不敢敲门
I'm too nervous to knock
而且咱都没完全认识他
We don't really know him
万一他是那种老是受苦的艺术家
What if he's one of those suffering artist types
而且还沉迷于巫术呢
who are into witchcraft?
万一他是食人族  想吃我们呢
Or what if he's a cannibal and wants to eat us?
万一他是食人族  不想吃我们呢
What if he's a cannibal and doesn't want to eat us?
不能忍受这种耻辱啊
We couldn't live with the shame
快跑
Run
助步器老头
Old Man Walker?
他在圈圈家干嘛
What's he doing in Hoops' house?
可能我们找错房子了
Maybe we got the wrong house
他没收到邮件  非常难过
He's sad that he got no mail
因为全被我收走了
That's 'cause I got it
收件者是圈圈
It's addressed to Hoops
就是这里没错
This is the right place
藻床笨笨
小朋友
房子里全是藻床小朋友的周边
The whole house is filled with "Kelpbed Kid" stuff
就好像在出演节目一样
It's just like being in the show
进来吧
Come on in
可疑鱼钩
我就不介意了
Don't mind if I do
怎么回事
What's happening?
为了圈圈好
那是圈圈吗
Is that Hoops?
不对
No
还是助步器老头
It's Old Man Walker again
忘了吗
Remember?
先前开邮箱那位
From the mailbox?
对啊
Oh, yeah
流氓
Hooligans
骗子
Swindlers
偷信贼
Letter looters
我们没想对你干坏事
We didn't mean any harm
只是想见见圈圈
We just wanted to meet Hoops
我们是粉丝
We're fans
我们爱圈圈
We love Hoops
圈圈
Hoops?
怎么不早说
Why didn't you say so?
我就是圈圈
I'm Hoops
好吧  老头子
Okay, old man
虽然不想说得这么直
I hate to break it to you
但圈圈是个小朋友
but Hoops is a little kid
没错  我小时候就是圈圈
Yup, I was Hoops when I was a little kid
已经是多年前的事了
many years ago
你是在说有很多年了吗
You're telling me there have been many years?
我不信
I don't believe it
没错  都是过去的事了
Yes, it was in the past
你怕是想把我们骗过去吧
I think you're trying to "past" one over on us
骗过去
"Past" one over
我没听懂
I don't get it
你们又算老几  呆呆小呆瓜
What are you, a couple of dizzy ding dongs?
他说了圈圈的口头禅
He said Hoops' catchphrase
呆呆小呆瓜
"Ya dizzy ding dongs"
Ya dizzy ding dongs
派大星  助步器老头就是圈圈
Patrick, "Old Man" Walker is Hoops
只是稍微有点  腐烂了
He just kinda, sorta, decayed
圈圈
Hoops
我们爱你
We love you
你快害我骨折了
You're breaking my bones
他有新的口头禅了
He's got a new catchphrase
什么声音
What was that?
是我的心脏吗
Was that my heart?
不对  是外面传来的
No, it was outside
我心脏跑外面了
My heart's outside?
又来了
Not again
好吃
Yum
真该死
Dagnabbit
是那个恶棍  阿贾克斯麦基
it's that ruffian, Ajax McGee
阿贾克斯
Ajax?
他不是藻床小朋友那位坏小孩吗
Isn't he the mean kid in "The Kelpbed Kids" show?
从前是
He was
现在他长成坏大人了
Now he's the mean adult
就住在荫凉滩疗养院里
at Shady Shoals Retirement Home
当个藻床小朋友就是这么个下场
That's what you get for being a Kelpbed Kid
圈圈讨厌鬼
Hoops the Poops
经典
Classic
我想到了
I just had an idea
复仇
Revenge
反击阿贾克斯  复现你演过的剧集
Let's get back at Ajax, like in one of your episodes
恶疾
Episodes?
对啊
Yeah
我这年纪确实发作了很多次恶疾
at my age, I have a lot of episodes
谁想吃布丁
Who wants pudding?
我想
I do
别布丁了
Hold that pudding
我们可以自制坦克
We can build our own tank
用藻床小朋友法集齐材料
and we'll gather material "The Kelpbed Kids" way
什么床谁了
The what bed who--
等等  什么
wait, what?
不愧是圈圈
Classic Hoops
三轮车游行
我们来找你了  阿贾克斯麦基
We're coming for you, Ajax McGee
凶巴巴撕碎机
跟我的凶巴巴撕碎机问个好
Say hello to my Meanie Mangler
荫凉滩疗养院
到了  圈圈
Here we are, Hoops
荫凉滩
Shady Shoals
来叫阿贾克斯出来
Now call out for Ajax
呼叫谁
Who am I calling?
对着这个讲
Talk into this
喂  接线生
Hello, operator?
这里是梭鱼4117
This is Barracuda 4117
处方备好了没
Is my prescription ready yet?
给我走开
23 Skiddoo
你哪找来的垃圾
Where did you get that pile of junk?
反正不关我事
Never mind, I don't care
吃点蛋吧
Have some eggs
准备大炮
Prepare cannon
开火
Fire
你这是拿面包装弹吗
You loaded the cannon with toast?
我吃面包都会配蛋
I always have toast with eggs
部署舔盐
Deploying salt lick
出动海牛
Engaging sea cow
你的舌头好粗糙
Your tongue is so rough
所有东西都有股面包味
Everything smells like toast
快看  阿贾克斯落荒而逃了
Look, there goes Ajax
下次一定会整到你们的
I'll get youse next time
呼唤我的名字
Say my name
我就是讨厌鬼圈圈
I'm Hoops the Poops
经典
Classic
史上最棒藻床小朋友大冒险
Best "Kelpbed Kids" adventure ever
击掌
High four
叫我圈圈哎哟喂好了
Just call me Hoops the Oops
凤尾鱼宝宝
编剧
分镜总监
翻译: 1440kHz
指导总监
动画总监
统筹
监制
本字幕仅限学习交流
严禁用于商业用途
蟹堡王
好了好了  一个一个来
Okay, okay, one at a time
蟹黄堡
Krabby Patty
蟹黄堡来了
Krabby Patty, up
蟹黄堡
Krabby Patty
蟹黄堡来了
Krabby Patty, up
咪咪声都快逼疯我了  蟹老板
All this meeping is gonna drive me cuckoo, Mr. Krabs
他们咪了  你才有工资拿
All these meeps are paying your salary
咪就是钱
Meeps are money
蟹黄堡
Krabby Patty
蟹黄堡来了
Krabby Patty, up
等下  有人点了蟹黄堡打包外带
Wait, someone ordered a Krabby Patty to-go
谁点了蟹黄堡打包外带
Who ordered a Krabby Patty to-go?
等一下  这是谁点的
Wait, whose order is this?
好
Okay
不好意思  有没有谁点了蟹
Pardon me, did someone order a Krabby--
不好意思
My bad
我是说  咪咪
I meant meep, meep
高菲高伯
好耶  冰淇咪
Oh boy, ice meep
墨镜
好
Yeah
太咪了  酷哥
Real meep, daddy-o
床垫
弹弹跳跳
Bouncy, bouncy
我爱咪咪
I love to meep
海绵宝宝
Hey, SpongeBob
我的手掌要来认真玩拍手烤蛋糕了
These palms are ready to play some serious patty-cake
拍手烤蛋糕可不能缺了蛋糕
And you can't play patty-cake without cake
拍拍手  烤蛋糕
Patty-cake, patty-cake
烘焙师傅  我要快快吃蛋糕
Baker's man, I'll eat the cake as fast as I can
妈妈打电话找医生  医生说
Mama called the doctor, and the doctor said
别又烤蛋糕又在床上跳
"No more patty-cakes jumping on the bed"
邮递员
Mailman
早安  海绵宝宝
Morning, SpongeBob
早安  派大星
Morning, Patrick
不要
No
早该来上班了  海绵宝宝
It's about time, SpongeBob
迟到宝宝还差不多
LateBob is more like it
迟到宝宝
LateBob
既然你哼哼完了
When you're done snorting
我要来点个蟹黄堡
I'd like to order a Krabby Patty
好  等一下
Okay, hold on
来个蟹黄堡  海绵宝宝
One Krabby Patty, SpongeBob
海绵宝宝  别咪了
SpongeBob, stop that meeping
你以为你什么啊
What do you think you are?
凤尾鱼吗
An anchovy?
我听到咪咪而来的钱声了
I hear money meeps
凤尾鱼回来了吗
Are the anchovies back?
是海绵宝宝
It's SpongeBob
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob
到底怎么回事
What in the barnacles is going on here?
给我让开  让我珍贵的菲菲过路
Step aside and let my precious Fifi pass
不然就要冒犯到我了
or I will be offended
一堆人咪过来了
It's a stamp-meep
突发新闻
我是鲍勃盖尔多普勒  播报天气情况
Bob Gale Doppler, with the big weather
明天裤头村将会晴空万里
And I'd like to report it's sunny skies for Bikini Bottom
但今天正相反
But not today
即将发布一场暴风雨预警
cause there's a storm warning coming at ya
西南方向正吹来一阵凤伪鱼狂风
We got a gust of faux-chovies
coming in from the southwest
现在来实地探访一下  有请现场记者
Now with a closer look, here's our man on the street
金鱼鲁布
Rube Goldfish
感谢盖尔
Thanks, Gale
我身边的正是这群凤伪鱼
I'm here with the faux-chovies
他们造成了这场咪咪混乱
that are causing all this meep-abaloo
现在来问问大家十分关切的问题
Now I just have to ask the question
everyone wants to know
咪  到底是什么意思呢
What in the world does "meep" mean?
太咪了
Ameeping
感谢鲁布
Thanks Rube
所以如果今天不想变成凤尾鱼
So if you don't wanna turn into an anchovy today
建议待在室内
you're advised to stay indoors
等到凤伪鱼气压系统过境之后才出来
until that faux-chovy pressure system moves away
开
关
现在是章鱼哥专属的时间
And now it's Squiddy time
蛋黄酱
客人全跑光
When the customers fizzle
章鱼晒日光
the octopus will sizzle
好
Yeah
吃的  吃的
Dinner, dinner
海绵宝宝跟蟹老板变成凤伪鱼了
SpongeBob and Mr. Krabs are faux-chovies?
咪了很多声之后
好好好
Okay, okay
慢慢来
Slow down
一份蟹黄堡  一份蟹黄堡
One Krabby Patty, one Krabby Patty
想要蟹黄堡的都举手
Whoever wants a Krabby Patty, raise your hand
我带着耳机听不见你们咪咪叫
I can't hear your meeping with these headphones on
感谢海神王
Thank Neptune
不要
No
别弄坏我的耳机啊
Not my headphones
咪咪声
The meeps
难听的咪咪声全让我听到了
I can hear the horrible meeps
饿
Hungry
又咪
More meeps?
凤尾鱼打群架
Anchovy rumble
不好意思
My bad
我是说  咪咪
I meant meep, meep
我就知道是你
I thought that was you
全世界都疯了
The whole world has gone insane
再也受不了了
I can't take it anymore
不准再咪下去了
That is the last meep
匹萨店  特大匹萨
地面匹萨世界
Surface World of Pizza
想要点什么
What do you want?
我要来份特特特大号匹萨
I'd like an extra, extra, extra large pizza
尽快送来蟹堡王
sent to the Krusty Krab as soon as possible
要匹萨尽快送到
You want-a a pizza as soon-a as possible
没问题  小章鱼
you got it, Calimaro
谁都没法把我变成凤伪鱼
Nobody's turning me into a faux-chovy
匹萨外卖
Pizza delivery
匹萨
Pizza?
真香
That smells good
还以为会变凤伪鱼一辈子呢
I thought we'd never snap out of that faux-chovy thing
抱歉  蟹老板
Sorry, Mr. Krabs
差点没反应过来咪上头有多容易
I didn't realize how easy it is
to get swept up into a meep mentality
不怪你  小子
It's not your fault, boy-o
幸好匹萨是凤尾鱼的天敌
We're just lucky
that pizza is the anchovies' natural enemy
对啊  订派的那位救了我们的命
Yeah, whoever ordered that pie saved our lives
这好东西可不能浪费
And we shouldn't let it go to waste
还热乎着呢
It's still hot
什么
What?
没加凤尾鱼
No anchovies?
之前老是咪  害我也都饿了
All that meeping made me hungry too
章鱼哥先生  给咱来几张纸盘
Mr. Squidward, we need some paper plates out here
章鱼哥
Squidward?
在吗
Are you here?
那个懒鬼跑哪混了
Now just where is that lazy bum
刚刚明明一堆事
while all this is going on?